<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JadeBot&#39;s JadeDocs</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JadeBot&#39;s JadeDocs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Command List</title>
      <link>/docs/commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/commands/</guid>
      <description> Summary A quick list of all possible commands JadeBot responds to!
Commands  ==&amp;gt; About Avatar Booru Command Commands Credits Discord Dog Help Invite Markov MSPA OTP Pester Ship Wiki  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips &amp; Tricks</title>
      <link>/docs/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tips/</guid>
      <description>Command Correction JadeBot now takes commands ==&amp;gt;LikeThis like most other discord bots, but she displays a helpful message if you accidentally write it ==&amp;gt; LikeThis.
Fake Pesterlogs When you enter an empty ==&amp;gt;, JadeBot will say a line randomly generated using all of Jade&amp;rsquo;s Pesterlogs.
Responses JadeBot has a bunch of cute responses to various phrases in any message she can read. This cannot currently be turned off, but eventually a server admin may opt-out their server from her responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avatar</title>
      <link>/docs/avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/avatar/</guid>
      <description>Summary Avatar grabs a picture of a user&amp;rsquo;s avatar. Their actual username and discord tag will display below. Usage Default ==&amp;gt;avatar JadeBot displays a picture of your own avatar.
Arguments ==&amp;gt;avatar @nickname JadeBot displays a picture of the @&amp;rsquo;d user&amp;rsquo;s avatar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog</title>
      <link>/docs/dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/dog/</guid>
      <description>Summary Dog displays pictures of dogs, which are taken from dog.ceo. You can contribute your own dog here. You can find a full list of breeds here.
Usage Default ==&amp;gt;dog JadeBot shows a random picture of a dog.
1 Argument ==&amp;gt;dog generalized_breed JadeBot will show dogs from a generalized category.
2 Arguments ==&amp;gt;dog specific breed Typing a breed in full will narrow your search to only those types of dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSPA/Booru</title>
      <link>/docs/mspa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mspa/</guid>
      <description>Summary Booru grabs a random image from mspabooru.org. JadeBot will respond to this command from both ==&amp;gt;mspa and ==&amp;gt;booru. Images will always be pulled from the 25 most recent images from that search result.
The Source link will link to the referenced source in the mspabooru.org post. Some sources will be to dead links, some sources may be NSFW; Art without a source will instead lead to the mspabooru page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ship/otp</title>
      <link>/docs/ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/ship/</guid>
      <description>Summary Ship ranks how canon your OTP is. You can call it from either `ship` or `otp`.
Usage Default ==&amp;gt;ship ==&amp;gt;otp JadeBot cannot rate what does not exist. JadeBot needs some input to for her to judge canonicity.
Arguments ==&amp;gt;ship yourshiphere ==&amp;gt;otp yourshiphere JadeBot will decree how likely something will be canon, from 0 to 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki</title>
      <link>/docs/wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/wiki/</guid>
      <description>Summary Wiki searches for articles on the [MSPA Wiki](https://mspaintadventures.fandom.com/wiki/MS_Paint_Adventures_Wiki).
Usage Default wiki JadeBot needs an article search for; she cannot search without input.
Arguments wiki jade harley JadeBot will return a 1 paragraph summary as well as a link to the article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Commands</title>
      <link>/docs/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/other/</guid>
      <description>Summary JadeBot has a lot of simple commands that don&#39;t require any input from you. Here is where you can find what they do.
Usage About ==&amp;gt;about ==&amp;gt;credits About displays a short accreditation blurb for JadeBot. You can also call it from credits.
Discord ==&amp;gt;discord Discord displays a link to the JadeBot discord server.
Help You complete the cycle of stupidity, as you arrive at the very command that brought you here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>