<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on JadeBot&#39;s JadeDocs</title>
    <link>/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on JadeBot&#39;s JadeDocs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki</title>
      <link>/docs/wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/wiki/</guid>
      <description>Summary Wiki searches for articles on the MSPA Wiki.
Usage Default wiki JadeBot needs an input to read a wiki article.
wiki jade harley JadeBot will return a 1 paragraph summary as well as a link to the article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avatar</title>
      <link>/docs/avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/avatar/</guid>
      <description>Summary Avatar grabs a picture of a user&amp;rsquo;s avatar. Their actual username and discord tag will display below.
Usage Default ==&amp;gt;avatar JadeBot displays a picture of your own avatar.
Arguments ==&amp;gt;avatar @nickname JadeBot displays a picture of an @&amp;rsquo;d user&amp;rsquo;s avatar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog</title>
      <link>/docs/dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/dog/</guid>
      <description>Summary Dog displays pictures of dogs, which are taken from dog.ceo. You can contribute your own dog here. You can find a full list of dogs here.
Usage Default ==&amp;gt;dog JadeBot shows a random picture of a dog.
1 Argument ==&amp;gt;dog generalized_breed JadeBot will show dogs from a generalized category.
2 Arguments ==&amp;gt;dog specific breed Typing a breed in full will narrow your search to only those types of dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSPA/Booru</title>
      <link>/docs/mspa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 12:00:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mspa/</guid>
      <description>Summary Booru grabs a random image from mspabooru.org. JadeBot will respond to this command from both ==&amp;gt;mspa and ==&amp;gt;booru. Images will always be pulled from the 25 most recent images from that search result.
The Source link will link to the referenced source in the mspabooru.org post. Some sources will be to dead links, some sources may be NSFW; Art without a source will instead lead to the mspabooru page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>